Samuel Gledhill

Profile

Highly motivated Full-Stack Developer with a passion for bringing UX design to life. With just over 2 years experience building responsive and accessible websites within the NHS, I am now looking for my next opportunity to further develop and apply my skill set.

Employment History

Junior Full-Stack Web Developer at Dene Healthcare, Leeds

January 2022 — Present

- Developed a web application to monitor the safe distribution of pharmaceuticals.
- Design and develop responsive and accessible websites.
- Develop and maintain web applications that streamline daily operations across various sectors within the organisation.
- · Collaborate with clients to accomplish their digital objectives.

Digital Development at Dene Healthcare, Leeds

January 2021 — January 2022

- Manage and maintain WordPress websites for over 150 clients.
- Setup and construct new WordPress websites.
- Manage and setup cloud web servers.
- Work with clients to implement changes and improvements to WordPress websites.
- Handle Domain DNS configuration.
- Learn and develop skills in HTML, CSS and numerous programming languages.

Sales Support at Dene Healthcare, Leeds

July 2015 — December 2020

- Increase spend of targeted customers.
- Maintain and improve customer relationships.
- Work with the sales team to implement and assist with sales strategies.
- Provide a high quality of customer service over the phone and face to face.

Education

Sir Titus Salt School

September 2006 — July 2013

A Levels

- Medical Science Merit
- Business Studies Merit
- Further Business Studies Merit

GCSE

• 8 GCSEs A-C Including English, Maths, Science and IT.

Details

Silsden West Yorkshire 07479470962 samgledhill1695@hotmail.com

Links

Portfolio - sgdeveloper.co.uk

Skills

JavaScript

PHP

HTML, CSS3

Frameworks: Laravel, React, Next JS, Tailwind, Bootstrap

Git

MVC

ORM

Building and working with RESTful API's

SQL and working with databases

Server management with Plesk